Contact

dishankit123@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abhishek-dishankit-807501148 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C++

Leadership

Data structures and algorithms

Certifications

Internet Connection: How to Get Online?

CODATHON

Algorithm Toolbox

Python Data Structures

Engineering virtual internship

Honors-Awards

Snack Down 2017

SnackDown 2019

Google Kick Start

Google Code Jam

Best Internship Project - AIR Division(Amadeus Labs)

Abhishek Dishankit

Software Engineer at Amadeus Labs

Bengaluru

Summary

GitHub: https://github.com/abhidish123

Personal Portfolio website:

https://abhidish123.github.io/adishankit-Portfolio/

A FullStack software developer with strong passion for selfimprovement, skilled in Data structures and algorithms, and love to make innovation in building new products.

Professional work experience with:-

- 1. Frontend AngularJS, HTML, JavaScript, CSS/SCSS
- 2. Backend C++, Python(Flask), NodeJS
- 3. Dev Tools Git, Bash scripting

Experience

Amadeus Labs

Software Engineer

August 2020 - Present (3 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Microsoft

Engineering Virtual Internship June 2020 - June 2020 (1 month)

India

Amadeus Labs

Intern

January 2020 - May 2020 (5 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Ericsson

CAREER CONNECT PROGRAM

March 2019 - March 2019 (1 month)

Vit Vellore

This Telecom Essentials program is delivered over 3 days with theoretical instructor-led lessons undertaken in a classroom environment. In approximately 20 hours, it focuses on Telecom fundamentals, Overview of next generation networks , Ip-Fication /Everything over IP and Emerging technologies.

Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited Summer Inernship May 2018 - June 2018 (2 months) Ghāziābād Area, India

Education

Vellore Institute of Technology
Bachelor of Technology , Electronics and Communications
Engineering · (2016 - 2020)

Bal Bharti School, Bahadurgarh
High School, Mathematics and Computer Science · (2009 - 2016)